let questions = [{"numb": 1, "question": "n\u00f6tig", "answer": "necessary, required", "options": ["fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "joyful, santoshita", "area, Kshetra", "necessary, required"]}, {"numb": 2, "question": "Ablauf", "answer": "Procedure", "options": ["Riot, galabhe", "Procedure", "particular, nirdishtavada", "sign"]}, {"numb": 3, "question": "Besch\u00e4ftigung", "answer": "Occupation", "options": ["fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "abuse, DurbaLake", "non violence, ahimse", "Occupation"]}, {"numb": 4, "question": "grundlegend", "answer": "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "options": ["communal, komu", "marketing", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "defeat, solu"]}, {"numb": 5, "question": "Segen", "answer": "Blessings, verb is SegNen", "options": ["area, Kshetra", "imemdiately, tatkshana", "Blessings, verb is SegNen", "Fuel, Indhana"]}, {"numb": 6, "question": "st\u00e4ndig", "answer": "constantly, nirantaravagi", "options": ["Hectic", "constantly, nirantaravagi", "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre", "Procedure"]}, {"numb": 7, "question": "durchsichtig", "answer": "transparent, paradarhska", "options": ["compulsory", "transparent, paradarhska", "against nature, aswabhavika", "opinion, view, abhipraya, nota"]}, {"numb": 8, "question": "brutal", "answer": "violent, himsatmaka", "options": ["violent, himsatmaka", "communal, komu", "violent, himsatmaka", "Cheat, Vanchane, Mosa"]}, {"numb": 9, "question": "Freundschaft", "answer": "friendship", "options": ["joyful, nagumogada", "friendship", "forever, shashwata", "operations, business, firm"]}, {"numb": 10, "question": "Ernst", "answer": "serious, Gambhira", "options": ["opinion, view, abhipraya, nota", "opposition,", "serious, Gambhira", "illegal, kanoonu bahira"]}, {"numb": 11, "question": "Abdruck", "answer": "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre", "options": ["area, Kshetra", "attention, Gamana", "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre", "illegal, kanoonu bahira"]}, {"numb": 12, "question": "Gewalt", "answer": "violence, Himse, dourjanya", "options": ["corresponding, anuroopavada", "opposition,", "violence, Himse, dourjanya", "contact person, samparka vyakti"]}, {"numb": 13, "question": "dauerhaft", "answer": "permanent, shashwata", "options": ["permanent, shashwata", "adjective, Perfect, paripoorna", "pramaanikarisida, dhrudikarisida", "strategy"]}, {"numb": 14, "question": "Fachbereich", "answer": "department, vibhaga", "options": ["department, vibhaga", "purposefully, uddeshapporvakavagi", "Challenge", "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre"]}, {"numb": 15, "question": "Fortschritt", "answer": "abhivraddhi, progress", "options": ["Cheat, Vanchane, Mosa", "necessary, required", "Nature", "abhivraddhi, progress"]}, {"numb": 16, "question": "Prozess", "answer": "process, kannada: prakriye", "options": ["process, kannada: prakriye", "Procedure", "waste, garbage", "overview, pakshinota, avalokana"]}, {"numb": 17, "question": "Verfahren", "answer": "Procedure", "options": ["Procedure", "Hate, Dwesha", "Fuel, Indhana", "approach, strategy"]}, {"numb": 18, "question": "laut + dativ, laut + gen", "answer": "according to..", "options": ["torture, chitrahimse", "joyful, santoshadayaka", "according to..", "enmity, Vairatva"]}, {"numb": 19, "question": "widerstand", "answer": "resist, virdoshisu, tadedu nillisu", "options": ["prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "abuse, DurbaLake", "resist, virdoshisu, tadedu nillisu", "Opportunity"]}, {"numb": 20, "question": "Strategie", "answer": "strategy", "options": ["Globalization", "strategy", "loneliness", "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre"]}, {"numb": 21, "question": "ben\u00f6tigt", "answer": "necessary, required", "options": ["according to..", "department, vibhaga", "Kaavos, Kannda: Gondala", "necessary, required"]}, {"numb": 22, "question": "Herausforderung", "answer": "Challenge", "options": ["Challenge", "sight, drushti", "Greenhouse effekt", "Blessings, verb is SegNen"]}, {"numb": 23, "question": "betroffene", "answer": "affected, concerned, baadhitha", "options": ["available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku", "affected, concerned, baadhitha", "joyful, santoshita", "Victory, Jaya"]}, {"numb": 24, "question": "Infrastruktur", "answer": "Infrastructure", "options": ["imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre", "political, raajakiya", "Covert (Religion)", "Infrastructure"]}, {"numb": 25, "question": "Ansicht", "answer": "opinion, view, abhipraya, nota", "options": ["opinion, view, abhipraya, nota", "prespective, Viewpoint, Drustikona", "caution, precaution, ecchara, jagarookate", "logic, tarka"]}, {"numb": 26, "question": "Friede", "answer": "peace, shaanti", "options": ["abuse, DurbaLake", "forever, shashwata", "necessary, required", "peace, shaanti"]}, {"numb": 27, "question": "Niederlage", "answer": "defeat, solu", "options": ["abhivraddhi, progress", "Hectic", "imemdiately, tatkshana", "defeat, solu"]}, {"numb": 28, "question": "Menschheit", "answer": "humanity", "options": ["Greenhouse effekt", "humanity", "improvment", "ashyakara, disgusting"]}, {"numb": 29, "question": "gem\u00e4\u00df+dativ", "answer": "according to..", "options": ["according to..", "Carbon monooxide", "political, raajakiya", "non violence, ahimse"]}, {"numb": 30, "question": "Konvertierung", "answer": "Covert (Religion)", "options": ["Covert (Religion)", "KaruNe, Daye", "abuse, DurbaLake", "No response given"]}, {"numb": 31, "question": "Kohlenstoffmonoxid", "answer": "Carbon monooxide", "options": ["approval", "Hectic", "Carbon monooxide", "operations, business, firm"]}, {"numb": 32, "question": "Genehmigung", "answer": "approval", "options": ["compulsory", "defeat, solu", "according to..", "approval"]}, {"numb": 33, "question": "Stoff", "answer": "Fuel, Indhana", "options": ["Fuel, Indhana", "deadly", "political, raajakiya", "Victory, Jaya"]}, {"numb": 34, "question": "wesentlich", "answer": "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "options": ["garbage", "Infrastructure", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "Blessings, verb is SegNen"]}, {"numb": 35, "question": "gewaltsam", "answer": "violent, himsatmaka", "options": ["lonely", "approval", "violent, himsatmaka", "adjective, Perfect, paripoorna"]}, {"numb": 36, "question": "Beteiligung", "answer": "involvement", "options": ["impaired, disabled", "necessary, required", "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre", "involvement"]}, {"numb": 37, "question": "Ma\u00dfnahme", "answer": "Krama, Measure", "options": ["Procedure", "necessary, required", "Krama, Measure", "joyful, santoshita"]}, {"numb": 38, "question": "Fr\u00f6hlich", "answer": "joyful, nagumogada", "options": ["joy, santosha", "joyful, nagumogada", "opinion, abhipraya", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi"]}, {"numb": 39, "question": "verbrauch", "answer": "kannada: Sevane, consumption", "options": ["sight, drushti", "kannada: Sevane, consumption", "dignity, Ghanathe", "purposefully, uddeshapporvakavagi"]}, {"numb": 40, "question": "Freude", "answer": "joy, santosha", "options": ["process, kannada: prakriye", "Victory, Jaya", "joy, santosha", "political, raajakiya"]}, {"numb": 41, "question": "politisch", "answer": "political, raajakiya", "options": ["Modernization", "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre", "dignity, Ghanathe", "political, raajakiya"]}, {"numb": 42, "question": "Froh", "answer": "joyful, santoshita", "options": ["Nature", "vehicle, vaahana", "joyful, santoshita", "approach, strategy"]}, {"numb": 43, "question": "Kommunikation", "answer": "communication", "options": ["communication", "Victory, Jaya", "Kaavos, Kannda: Gondala", "according to.."]}, {"numb": 44, "question": "grunds\u00e4tzlich", "answer": "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "options": ["available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku", "Greenhouse effekt", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "sign"]}, {"numb": 45, "question": "inzwischen", "answer": "meanwhile, ee naduve, ashtralli", "options": ["peace, shaanti", "necessary, required", "meanwhile, ee naduve, ashtralli", "purposefully, uddeshapporvakavagi"]}, {"numb": 46, "question": "Digitalizierung", "answer": "Digitalization", "options": ["fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "ashyakara, disgusting", "Nature", "Digitalization"]}, {"numb": 47, "question": "vorsicht", "answer": "caution, precaution, ecchara, jagarookate", "options": ["spokesperson, vaktaar", "area, Bhoopradesha", "torture, chitrahimse", "caution, precaution, ecchara, jagarookate"]}, {"numb": 48, "question": "Gelegenheit", "answer": "Opportunity", "options": ["Guideline, Kannada: Maargasoochi", "process, kannada: prakriye", "non violence, ahimse", "Opportunity"]}, {"numb": 49, "question": "unmittelbar", "answer": "immediate, takshanavagi", "options": ["deadly", "immediate, takshanavagi", "sign", "necessary, required"]}, {"numb": 50, "question": "Beglaubigte", "answer": "pramaanikarisida, dhrudikarisida", "options": ["pramaanikarisida, dhrudikarisida", "process, kannada: prakriye", "abhivraddhi, progress", "dignity, Ghanathe"]}, {"numb": 51, "question": "Grundsatz", "answer": "Policy", "options": ["logic, tarka", "Policy", "constantly, nirantaravagi", "necessary, required"]}, {"numb": 52, "question": "Ressource", "answer": "resource, sampanmoola", "options": ["improvment", "resource, sampanmoola", "sign", "department, ilaakhe"]}, {"numb": 53, "question": "Schild, Schilder", "answer": "sign", "options": ["Globalization", "Carbon", "sign", "prespective, Viewpoint, Drustikona"]}, {"numb": 54, "question": "notwending", "answer": "necessary, required", "options": ["caution, precaution, ecchara, jagarookate", "violence, Himse, dourjanya", "necessary, required", "peace, shaanti"]}, {"numb": 55, "question": "pl\u00f6tzlich", "answer": "suddenly, idakiddante, akaasmat", "options": ["serious, Gambhira", "dignity, Ghanathe", "Nature", "suddenly, idakiddante, akaasmat"]}, {"numb": 56, "question": "Lebensw\u00fcrdigkeit", "answer": "KaruNe, Daye", "options": ["similar, holuva, samavada", "according to..", "constantly, nirantaravagi", "KaruNe, Daye"]}, {"numb": 57, "question": "Voraussetzung", "answer": "prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "options": ["prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "deadly", "adjective, Perfect, paripoorna", "affected, concerned, baadhitha"]}, {"numb": 58, "question": "logik", "answer": "logic, tarka", "options": ["particular, nirdishtavada", "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "area, Bhoopradesha", "logic, tarka"]}, {"numb": 59, "question": "Meinung", "answer": "opinion, abhipraya", "options": ["opinion, abhipraya", "necessary, required", "communal, komu", "puprose, uddeesha"]}, {"numb": 60, "question": "der Hass", "answer": "Hate, Dwesha", "options": ["Hate, Dwesha", "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre", "Carbon", "sarasari"]}, {"numb": 61, "question": "Hectisch", "answer": "Hectic", "options": ["necessary, required", "Hectic", "Globalization", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi"]}, {"numb": 62, "question": "prinzipiell", "answer": "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "options": ["compulsory", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "communication", "opinion, view, abhipraya, nota"]}, {"numb": 63, "question": "Klima", "answer": "Nature", "options": ["Victory, Jaya", "immediate, takshanavagi", "Nature", "serious, Gambhira"]}, {"numb": 64, "question": "sofort", "answer": "imemdiately, tatkshana", "options": ["fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "sign", "imemdiately, tatkshana", "process, kannada: prakriye"]}, {"numb": 65, "question": "Chaos", "answer": "Kaavos, Kannda: Gondala", "options": ["fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "attentive", "Kaavos, Kannda: Gondala", "improvment"]}, {"numb": 66, "question": "t\u00f6dlich", "answer": "deadly", "options": ["caution, precaution, ecchara, jagarookate", "deadly", "Blessings, verb is SegNen", "area, Kshetra"]}, {"numb": 67, "question": "aktiv", "answer": "active, sakriya, chatuvatikeyindiru", "options": ["fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "active, sakriya, chatuvatikeyindiru", "joyful, nagumogada", "dignity, Ghanathe"]}, {"numb": 68, "question": "Treibhauseffekt", "answer": "Greenhouse effekt", "options": ["illegal, kanoonu bahira", "Greenhouse effekt", "sight, drushti", "vehicle, vaahana"]}, {"numb": 69, "question": "Verwendung", "answer": "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "options": ["imemdiately, tatkshana", "peace, shaanti", "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "active, sakriya, chatuvatikeyindiru"]}, {"numb": 70, "question": "Kommunal", "answer": "communal, komu", "options": ["Procedure", "communal, komu", "process, kannada: prakriye", "resist, virdoshisu, tadedu nillisu"]}, {"numb": 71, "question": "entsprechende", "answer": "corresponding, anuroopavada", "options": ["enmity, Vairatva", "sarasari", "corresponding, anuroopavada", "carbon dioxide"]}, {"numb": 72, "question": "Richtlinie", "answer": "Guideline, Kannada: Maargasoochi", "options": ["Guideline, Kannada: Maargasoochi", "Carbon monooxide", "involvement", "prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1"]}, {"numb": 73, "question": "Sauerstoff", "answer": "Oxygen", "options": ["enmity, Vairatva", "Oxygen", "active, sakriya, chatuvatikeyindiru", "violence, Himse, dourjanya"]}, {"numb": 74, "question": "Fehlerlos", "answer": "without problems", "options": ["compulsory", "operations, business, firm", "Victory, Jaya", "without problems"]}, {"numb": 75, "question": "Zustand state, condition, sthithi", "answer": "No response given", "options": ["approach, strategy", "meanwhile, ee naduve, ashtralli", "contact person, samparka vyakti", "No response given"]}, {"numb": 76, "question": "Sprecher/in", "answer": "spokesperson, vaktaar", "options": ["involvement", "spokesperson, vaktaar", "corresponding, anuroopavada", "improvment"]}, {"numb": 77, "question": "w\u00fcrdig", "answer": "dignified", "options": ["garbage", "impaired, disabled", "Opportunity", "dignified"]}, {"numb": 78, "question": "Nutzung", "answer": "Kannda: BaLake", "options": ["peaceful, shaantiyuta", "opposition,", "combination", "Kannda: BaLake"]}, {"numb": 79, "question": "ewig", "answer": "forever, shashwata", "options": ["forever, shashwata", "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre", "vehicle, vaahana", "dignified"]}, {"numb": 80, "question": "M\u00fcll", "answer": "garbage", "options": ["garbage", "communal, komu", "necessary, required", "purposefully, uddeshapporvakavagi"]}, {"numb": 81, "question": "Perspektiv", "answer": "prespective, Viewpoint, Drustikona", "options": ["prespective, Viewpoint, Drustikona", "KaruNe, Daye", "joyful, santoshita", "spokesperson, vaktaar"]}, {"numb": 82, "question": "Kohlenstoffdioxid", "answer": "carbon dioxide", "options": ["carbon dioxide", "political, raajakiya", "sight, drushti", "involvement"]}, {"numb": 83, "question": "ehemalig", "answer": "Former, maaji", "options": ["Former, maaji", "temporary, taatkalika", "Fuel, Indhana", "KaruNe, Daye"]}, {"numb": 84, "question": "durchschnitt", "answer": "sarasari", "options": ["prerequisites, \u0caa\u0cc2\u0cb0\u0ccd\u0cb5\u0cbe\u0caa\u0cc7\u0c95\u0ccd\u0cb7\u0cbf\u0ca4\u0c97\u0cb3\u0cc1", "sarasari", "without problems", "approach, strategy"]}, {"numb": 85, "question": "Bereich", "answer": "area, Kshetra", "options": ["purposefully, uddeshapporvakavagi", "torture, chitrahimse", "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "area, Kshetra"]}, {"numb": 86, "question": "Ansprechpartner", "answer": "contact person, samparka vyakti", "options": ["fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "KaruNe, Daye", "Enviornment friendly", "contact person, samparka vyakti"]}, {"numb": 87, "question": "Qual", "answer": "torture, chitrahimse", "options": ["torture, chitrahimse", "overview, pakshinota, avalokana", "Modernization", "adjective, Perfect, paripoorna"]}, {"numb": 88, "question": "einwandfrei", "answer": "adjective, Perfect, paripoorna", "options": ["fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "Guideline, Kannada: Maargasoochi", "adjective, Perfect, paripoorna", "resource, sampanmoola"]}, {"numb": 89, "question": "Gewaltlosigkeit", "answer": "non violence, ahimse", "options": ["violent, himsatmaka", "impaired, disabled", "particular, nirdishtavada", "non violence, ahimse"]}, {"numb": 90, "question": "Vertrieb", "answer": "marketing", "options": ["enmity, Vairatva", "joyful, santoshita", "marketing", "particular, nirdishtavada"]}, {"numb": 91, "question": "Hindernis", "answer": "obstacle, ade tade", "options": ["adjective, Perfect, paripoorna", "obstacle, ade tade", "dignity, Ghanathe", "imprint, kaalachchu, Mudre"]}, {"numb": 92, "question": "\ufeffGlobalizierung", "answer": "Globalization", "options": ["Riot, galabhe", "according to..", "Globalization", "Digitalization"]}, {"numb": 93, "question": "Gegengrund", "answer": "Counter argument", "options": ["according to..", "necessary, required", "Counter argument", "Globalization"]}, {"numb": 94, "question": "erforderlich", "answer": "necessary, required", "options": ["constantly, nirantaravagi", "non violence, ahimse", "political, raajakiya", "necessary, required"]}, {"numb": 95, "question": "absichtlich", "answer": "purposefully, uddeshapporvakavagi", "options": ["Covert (Religion)", "need, Avashyakate", "joy, santosha", "purposefully, uddeshapporvakavagi"]}, {"numb": 96, "question": "Druck", "answer": "Pressure", "options": ["adjective, Perfect, paripoorna", "Nature", "Pressure", "communication"]}, {"numb": 97, "question": "Betrug", "answer": "Cheat, Vanchane, Mosa", "options": ["compulsory", "Procedure", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "Cheat, Vanchane, Mosa"]}, {"numb": 98, "question": "Abfall", "answer": "waste, garbage", "options": ["approach, strategy", "humanity", "Victory, Jaya", "waste, garbage"]}, {"numb": 99, "question": "Einsamkeit", "answer": "loneliness", "options": ["carbon dioxide", "loneliness", "defeat, solu", "department, ilaakhe"]}, {"numb": 100, "question": "Vorgehensweise", "answer": "approach, strategy", "options": ["torture, chitrahimse", "abuse, DurbaLake", "approach, strategy", "waste, garbage"]}, {"numb": 101, "question": "obligatorisch", "answer": "compulsory", "options": ["violence, Himse, dourjanya", "imemdiately, tatkshana", "compulsory", "resist, virdoshisu, tadedu nillisu"]}, {"numb": 102, "question": "widerrechtlich", "answer": "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "options": ["sarasari", "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "Opportunity", "Kaavos, Kannda: Gondala"]}, {"numb": 103, "question": "Einsam", "answer": "lonely", "options": ["No response given", "Procedure", "strategy", "lonely"]}, {"numb": 104, "question": "Anwendung", "answer": "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "options": ["Counter argument", "joyful, santoshadayaka", "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "Kaavos, Kannda: Gondala"]}, {"numb": 105, "question": "widernat\u00fcrlich", "answer": "against nature, aswabhavika", "options": ["immediate, takshanavagi", "Hate, Dwesha", "against nature, aswabhavika", "compulsory"]}, {"numb": 106, "question": "Vorgang", "answer": "process, kannada: prakriye", "options": ["constantly, nirantaravagi", "process, kannada: prakriye", "sign", "available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku"]}, {"numb": 107, "question": "befristet", "answer": "temporary, taatkalika", "options": ["fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "temporary, taatkalika", "necessary, required", "communal, komu"]}, {"numb": 108, "question": "Absicht", "answer": "puprose, uddeesha", "options": ["against nature, aswabhavika", "Policy", "puprose, uddeesha", "violence, Himse, dourjanya"]}, {"numb": 109, "question": "widerlich", "answer": "ashyakara, disgusting", "options": ["Former, maaji", "without problems", "political, raajakiya", "ashyakara, disgusting"]}, {"numb": 110, "question": "Fahrzeug", "answer": "vehicle, vaahana", "options": ["vehicle, vaahana", "joyful, santoshadayaka", "No response given", "sign"]}, {"numb": 111, "question": "Gebiet", "answer": "area, Kshetra", "options": ["fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "Nature", "area, Kshetra", "defeat, solu"]}, {"numb": 112, "question": "Modernizierung", "answer": "Modernization", "options": ["defeat, solu", "necessary, required", "Modernization", "Opportunity"]}, {"numb": 113, "question": "Friedlich", "answer": "peaceful, shaantiyuta", "options": ["available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku", "ashyakara, disgusting", "Kannda: BaLake", "peaceful, shaantiyuta"]}, {"numb": 114, "question": "Verf\u00fcgbar", "answer": "available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku", "options": ["necessary, required", "against nature, aswabhavika", "available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku", "waste, garbage"]}, {"numb": 115, "question": "Betrieb", "answer": "operations, business, firm", "options": ["department, vibhaga", "Carbon", "according to..", "operations, business, firm"]}, {"numb": 116, "question": "widerspruch", "answer": "opposition,", "options": ["joyful, nagumogada", "torture, chitrahimse", "Modernization", "opposition,"]}, {"numb": 117, "question": "\u00e4hnlich", "answer": "similar, holuva, samavada", "options": ["puprose, uddeesha", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "similar, holuva, samavada", "waste, garbage"]}, {"numb": 118, "question": "Natur", "answer": "Nature", "options": ["Oxygen", "resource, sampanmoola", "communal, komu", "Nature"]}, {"numb": 119, "question": "Umweltfreundlich", "answer": "Enviornment friendly", "options": ["Oxygen", "logic, tarka", "Enviornment friendly", "Policy"]}, {"numb": 120, "question": "sicht", "answer": "sight, drushti", "options": ["sight, drushti", "special, visheshavada", "sign", "ashyakara, disgusting"]}, {"numb": 121, "question": "Kombination", "answer": "combination", "options": ["combination", "Blessings, verb is SegNen", "department, ilaakhe", "Digitalization"]}, {"numb": 122, "question": "Feindschaft", "answer": "enmity, Vairatva", "options": ["impaired, disabled", "enmity, Vairatva", "usage  Kannada: BaLake,", "active, sakriya, chatuvatikeyindiru"]}, {"numb": 123, "question": "Pflicht", "answer": "compulsory", "options": ["Nature", "Greenhouse effekt", "compulsory", "active, sakriya, chatuvatikeyindiru"]}, {"numb": 124, "question": "Kohlenstoff", "answer": "Carbon", "options": ["abhivraddhi, progress", "available, kannada : Labhyavide, Doraku", "department, ilaakhe", "Carbon"]}, {"numb": 125, "question": "Bed\u00fcrfnis", "answer": "need, Avashyakate", "options": ["process, kannada: prakriye", "dignified", "logic, tarka", "need, Avashyakate"]}, {"numb": 126, "question": "Behindert", "answer": "impaired, disabled", "options": ["attention, Gamana", "imemdiately, tatkshana", "Krama, Measure", "impaired, disabled"]}, {"numb": 127, "question": "besondere", "answer": "special, visheshavada", "options": ["lonely", "special, visheshavada", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "against nature, aswabhavika"]}, {"numb": 128, "question": "bestimmt", "answer": "particular, nirdishtavada", "options": ["particular, nirdishtavada", "waste, garbage", "joyful, santoshita", "sarasari"]}, {"numb": 129, "question": "Abteilung", "answer": "department, ilaakhe", "options": ["necessary, required", "imemdiately, tatkshana", "adjective, Perfect, paripoorna", "department, ilaakhe"]}, {"numb": 130, "question": "illegal", "answer": "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "options": ["without problems", "illegal, kanoonu bahira", "pramaanikarisida, dhrudikarisida", "Occupation"]}, {"numb": 131, "question": "Erfolg", "answer": "Victory, Jaya", "options": ["necessary, required", "Hate, Dwesha", "Victory, Jaya", "improvment"]}, {"numb": 132, "question": "Sieg", "answer": "Victory, Jaya", "options": ["approach, strategy", "necessary, required", "Victory, Jaya", "Procedure"]}, {"numb": 133, "question": "widerwillig", "answer": "reluctant, manasillada", "options": ["defeat, solu", "fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "No response given", "reluctant, manasillada"]}, {"numb": 134, "question": "W\u00fcrde", "answer": "dignity, Ghanathe", "options": ["area, Kshetra", "KaruNe, Daye", "dignity, Ghanathe", "necessary, required"]}, {"numb": 135, "question": "elementar", "answer": "basic, fundamental", "options": ["fundamentally, kannada: Moolabhootavagi", "adjective, Perfect, paripoorna", "caution, precaution, ecchara, jagarookate", "basic, fundamental"]}, {"numb": 136, "question": "Randale", "answer": "Riot, galabhe", "options": ["necessary, required", "sight, drushti", "opinion, view, abhipraya, nota", "Riot, galabhe"]}, {"numb": 137, "question": "Aufmerksam", "answer": "attentive", "options": ["involvement", "resource, sampanmoola", "attentive", "Kaavos, Kannda: Gondala"]}, {"numb": 138, "question": "Freudig", "answer": "joyful, santoshadayaka", "options": ["violence, Himse, dourjanya", "constantly, nirantaravagi", "joyful, santoshadayaka", "Infrastructure"]}, {"numb": 139, "question": "\u00fcbersicht", "answer": "overview, pakshinota, avalokana", "options": ["dignified", "non violence, ahimse", "overview, pakshinota, avalokana", "Infrastructure"]}, {"numb": 140, "question": "Abnutzung", "answer": "abuse, DurbaLake", "options": ["abuse, DurbaLake", "permanent, shashwata", "Former, maaji", "Riot, galabhe"]}, {"numb": 141, "question": "Verlauf", "answer": "process, kannada: prakriye", "options": ["Digitalization", "process, kannada: prakriye", "Greenhouse effekt", "illegal, kanoonu bahira"]}, {"numb": 142, "question": "Aufmerksamkeit", "answer": "attention, Gamana", "options": ["Krama, Measure", "attention, Gamana", "overview, pakshinota, avalokana", "contact person, samparka vyakti"]}, {"numb": 143, "question": "Verbesserung", "answer": "improvment", "options": ["improvment", "strategy", "violent, himsatmaka", "Former, maaji"]}, {"numb": 144, "question": "Fl\u00e4che", "answer": "area, Bhoopradesha", "options": ["purposefully, uddeshapporvakavagi", "violence, Himse, dourjanya", "abuse, DurbaLake", "area, Bhoopradesha"]}];